eckeroline.com 2019-01-09

# Privacy and Cookie Policy | Eckerö Line

This privacy policy sets out how Eckerö Line's website (hereafter "the Service") uses and protects any information that you give the Service while using this website. The Service is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will be used in accordance with this privacy statement and policy. The Service may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

## What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * Name and contect information including mobile number and email address.
  * Demographic information such as post code, age and gender.
  * Your interests and preferences made in the Service.
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.

## What we do with the information we gather

We gather this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * Improving our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using different methods of communication.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, messages to mobile or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your device. The cookie helps analyse web traffic. Cookies allow web applications, like the Service, to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website. A cookie in no way gives us access to your device or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## Links to other websites

The Service may contain links to other websites. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, like the customer registration form, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes.
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time at the account admistration page or by choosing the unsubscribe link in the marketing message.

We will not sell or distribute your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please check your information in the account administration page or contant us.

## List of cookies we collect

The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

Cookie Name| Cookie Description  
---|---  
FORM_KEY | Stores randomly generated key used to prevent forged requests.  
PHPSESSID | Your session ID on the server.  
GUEST-VIEW | Allows guests to view and edit their orders.  
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART | A link to information about your cart and viewing history, if you have asked for this.  
STF | Information on products you have emailed to friends.  
STORE | The store view or language you have selected.  
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE | Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.  
MAGE-CACHE-SESSID | Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.  
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE | Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.  
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE-SECTION-INVALIDATION | Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.  
MAGE-CACHE-TIMEOUT | Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.  
SECTION-DATA-IDS | Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.  
PRIVATE_CONTENT_VERSION | Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.  
X-MAGENTO-VARY | Facilitates caching of content on the server to make pages load faster.  
MAGE-TRANSLATION-FILE-VERSION | Facilitates translation of content to other languages.  
MAGE-TRANSLATION-STORAGE | Facilitates translation of content to other languages.  
AUTOCOMPLETE | Used to save data from the quick search to optimise speed.  
AUTOCOMPLETE-PROVIDER | Used to save data from the quick search to optimise speed.  
AUTOCOMPLETE-RECENT | Used to save data from the quick search to optimise speed.  
SEARCHREPORT-LOG | Used to save data from the quick search to optimise speed.  
NREUM | Used to monitor the health of the web site.  
JSESSIONID | Used to monitor the health of the web site.
